it has been evident for some time now that this day had to come it was unavoidable
i'm sure that some of you may have already heard the news
but for the rest of you the moriartes face a crisis as yet unprecedented
so i hope you're ready for this lads it'll take all of our expertise to achieve a decisive victory
sorry i'm late have you already all for one and one for all right wait come again
i can't pull the street at night
行き詰まる君の視線に
i feel your sickness in your eyes
傷ついて壊していこう
終わりなきこのpunishment
i feel your sins
いつでも
抜かれられない take me away
i don't feel your love but i can give you love
目が覚めるような夢を見せてよ
目が覚めるたび君は崩れる
いつか
抜かれられる
見つけ出して
美容 heart
A tea party?
Yes.
As I'm sure you're aware,
tea parties are held by each household on a rotating basis.
I've had great success over the years,
politely declining the opportunity to host.
But the Earl of Rockwell recently founded in himself
to take me to task over it.
So it is with great reluctance, I must say,
it is finally time that our household
fulfill that particular duty as well.
He's really not making an effort to disguise
how much he truly hates this, is he?
We only have until this Sunday to prepare.
What major obstacles do we face?
I was just getting to that.
As you may recall,
there was once a few amongst the noble ladies
who had the temerity to sidle up to will,
under pretense of viewing a prize-winning rose garden.
I imagine we will see the same such ladies once again.
Those who view this merely as an opportunity
to approach men of stature.
I bet.
But that means you're in just as much danger as he is, aren't you?
Indeed.
Ordinarily, Will and I are more than capable of handling such situations.
However,
these women become quite unpredictable when they let their hair down,
and are emboldened even further in greater numbers.
It is this group psychology that is the issue.
We'll be overrun,
and then there is the house.
We have the operations room in the cellar,
and a collection of many other items
which must be kept private at any and all costs.
The challenge is to direct this tea party to a successful end,
free from any snooping noble eyes.
A battle not easily fought.
We'll have nearly a hundred guests here.
Far more than we'll be able to handle on our own.
We have no choice but to hire some temporary help.
Then obviously overseeing that help
is going to be necessary to plan for as well.
Dear brother,
might I ask you to supervise them?
I suppose so.
Understand that I can only give this particular role
to the person I trust the most.
Very well, then.
As long as I can be of help to you.
Perfect.
I'm afraid we won't be able to invite Patterson
due to his work obligations.
But Fred,
do reach out to Herder, won't you?
I believe I've just started the perfect post to assign him.
Sure.
I can do that.
All right.
Our task is to play ideal employees of an Earl's household
and send our guests home in good spirits with good stories.
Understood?
Right!
Hmm.
Ah, what perfect weather.
I've rallied the troops.
Right.
Now, let's review our charges one last time.
Once Albert concludes his remarks,
I will oversee our guests as they dine in the main venue.
I will supervise our temporary kitchen employees,
thus keeping my focus inside the estate.
And our set position will be right here in the garden.
Indeed, it will.
Well, we'll keep our eyes open and assist each other as needed.
I'm here primarily as bodyguard for you two.
As for me,
I'll entertain any guests who visit the Rose Garden.
And I will be here flitting about the grounds
until such a time that someone calls upon my expertise.
Correct.
You will be our hit-and-run attacker.
Your skills provide a sort of insurance against the unexpected.
We are marching into war, after all.
Well, that's a bit frightening.
Wait, did Hodor ever show himself?
Ah.
He's already on standby at his designated location.
My word.
Here I thought I'd been invited to a tea party,
and then I find out that I'm stuck in charge of these dingy quarters.
What do I have to do?
You'd think William would trust me a bit more at this point.
But he did say that I could do as I please down here,
as long as I listened carefully.
So I think I'll work on these delightful puzzle rings he gave me.
Ooh.
If I rotate this one like this...
To battle.
I've given up hope that this day would ever arise.
This is the Moriarty Estate Tea Party we've all been pining for.
And this is darling Albert and his middle brother William weren't enough on their own.
I've heard that even their servants have been looking.
Oh my.
They both fight the Enchanting Garden, don't they?
Come now, girls.
If we let this chance get away, we'll never get another one.
You're crazy now, love.
No need to get in front of me.
I'm not.
You're just crazy.
We have to sit as close as possible.
Then hurry up before the Ellens get ahead of us.
Hello, ladies.
We are honored by your presence here today.
They're beyond beautiful.
As you enter the grounds, please sign in at reception.
And there's no need to run.
As a result, please direct your gratitude to the Earl of Rockwell.
For it's thanks to him alone that we have welcomed you all here today.
I'm sure you're well aware, but we're quite a bashful bunch.
Despite all appearances, my brother William and I are nervous simply standing before you.
Now, we do hope you will avail yourselves of this opportunity to stop by our family's rose garden.
Our gardener has been hard at work, and we are pleased to see his roses have bloomed just in time to welcome you.
And we have plenty of snacks prepared for you as well.
Stay in chat for as long as time permits.
The second these remarks are over, I'm making a beeline straight for Albert.
And the moment he so dares to let go of his cup, I'm off to William!
These strong girls!
Without further ado, a toast to your health and to a most splendid day.
This pressure is intense.
Should I step in already?
He looks all right, but is he really?
I have been looking forward to conversing with all of you.
But with each of you talking over each other, I can't give you the attention you deserve.
I was under the impression that tea parties were a much more elegant affair.
An environment in which one can create bonds.
Share secrets.
Wouldn't that be nicer?
We have more than enough time, so please, do allow me to speak to you one by one.
Yes, the gentleman does make a very good point.
He does indeed.
I can scarce remember why we were in such a hurry in the first place.
Impressive work, Albert.
Pardon us.
We thought we'd go and have a look at the rose garden.
If you're not otherwise occupied, perhaps you'd like to join us?
I'm afraid I must decline.
My apologies, but I'm unable to leave my post here.
Oh, what a shame.
Another time.
Those broad shoulders.
Good luck in there, Fred.
Excuse me, Fred.
What sort of roses are these fluffy ones here?
Ah, yes.
They're a type of bourbon rose called boule de neige.
All bourbon roses have this shape, but these are cultivated for their color.
Their name means snowball.
I've never seen anything like them.
Are you the one who grew these gorgeous things?
I am.
And I'm glad you enjoy them.
Truly.
I'm flattered.
My roses.
I hope you're all right.
Those thorns can be nasty.
Oh, Fred.
Please, I assure you, I'm quite well.
See to your roses.
No, the roses are merely an addition.
An embellishment here to highlight your beauty.
And as such, I cannot allow them to bring harm to any of you.
Oh!
How dashing!
Much of the fervor outside has passed, so please make sure we have no shortage of snacks or tea as our guests find their calm.
Sir.
I'm terribly sorry, but I stumbled on my way out to the garden, and I shattered this lovely teapot.
You needn't spend your worries on a teapot.
Tell me, you're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine, sir.
And which guest had this been brewed for, my dear fellow?
Oh, it's... this was for the young master, William.
For brother.
Oh, then let's make him a fresh pot.
We will let it steep a bit longer.
Brother likes it strong, after all.
Now, then, if you would like to make the delivery, my friend, it should be just the right temperature by the time you pour it.
Yes, sir!
Oh, my! How's heaven there?
No! You wouldn't really go that far, would you?
Just imagine if anyone found out.
I'll worry about that if the time comes.
One must dig one's claws in, else no one will ever get any closer to them.
I suppose.
Dear lady, what's the rush?
I beg your pardon, ma'am.
Where on earth could she have gone?
All right, honey.
Things are proceeding smoothly enough.
I only hope that we can keep it up.
And on that note, how is William doing?
Simply keep that in mind and it shan't give you any trouble.
Wow. I never would have conceived of such a thing if not for you.
You have my gratitude.
Oh, William.
William, could I trouble you to advise me on my concern next?
But of course.
I'm afraid mine is a matter of the heart.
You see, there is a man whom I simply adore at the moment.
But I haven't the foggiest idea as to how to approach him.
All right.
Would you perchance be willing to tell me a bit more about this person?
Yes, indeed.
He's a mathematician and the younger brother of an earl.
And though I regrettably don't know him half as well as I would like,
I'm certain he is deeply kind.
Whenever I so much as think of this gentleman, my poor heart aches.
And naturally, I saw a doctor.
But he insisted that only William James Moriarty could possibly cure what hails me.
I grow more concerned by the hour.
They do say that lovesickness can be quite deadly, do they not?
Uh, yes.
I'm sure they do.
This ain't my circus, mate.
You're on your own.
Good luck, William.
Hmm?
Uh, I can't help you either.
An intruder in William's room.
Bond.
Oh, pardon me.
I must answer a call.
Oh, do come back.
I really think we should get out of here.
Oh, no.
I have to burn this room into my memories before I so much as think about leaving.
Look at all of this.
So many difficult-looking mathematics books.
By the looks of things, I suppose William really does spend most of his time in the study.
Oh?
What is this?
Oh, goodness.
They're as pretty as a painting.
How sublime they all are.
Look.
This must be William's walking stick.
Wait, perhaps we ought not.
Oh, my.
Look at this.
It's put together like a scabbit.
Ah!
Gracious.
That was silly.
So it was a magic wand all along.
I can't imagine why he'd keep a childish thing like this lying around.
My, my.
What naughty little kittens you must be to wander into a place such as this uninvited.
Now, why don't we return to the party?
Yes!
He is as handsome as all the rest!
May I ask you for your name?
Hush now.
You didn't even want to be here.
Ladies, please.
Let me have this one.
There's more than enough of me to go around.
I can't see.
We anticipated that someone would try to sneak into our rooms, and now I'm glad we did.
It's all set dressing up there.
There's nothing of any great import.
Could then.
But the one place that we really can't afford to be seen.
I don't know how she could have possibly made her way down here.
But she is quite the little explorer, so...
Someone's coming.
Albert was crystal clear that if, by some slim chance, anyone were to stumble upon this operations room, then I am authorized to neutralize them.
Regardless of who they are.
Where does this lead?
A wine cellar?
Oh, hello.
And who might you be?
If I may be honest, I was expecting a biped.
So let's have a look around, then, you and I.
This is awful.
Where in the world could she have gotten off to?
Is this who you were looking for?
Yes, it is.
Oh, dear, I thought I lost you.
You have my thanks, but may I ask who you are?
I am one of William's most prized employees.
A problem solver of the highest intellect.
Whenever he has a problem that deludes him, I am the one he calls upon.
I see.
And what's this?
That.
That is a leash that will extend up to 30 yards.
It seemed a perfect fit for this curious little girl, so you're more than welcome to keep it.
Truly?
How wonderful!
Thank you ever so much!
Of course.
But we should head back to the garden now.
Please, allow me to show you the way.
My word, what a perfectly charming way to spend an afternoon.
It was most enjoyable.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I'm so pleased to hear that you all had a good time.
We'll see you again soon.
I've just realized, I don't believe I saw Lewis Moriarty at all today.
Yes, I so wanted to speak with him.
Or at least see his face.
Perhaps next time.
Next time, indeed.
Nice work, brother.
And keeping Lewis away from the front lines was precisely the right decision.
Thank you.
It was an easy call.
We can't have the boy attracting unwanted lady friends.
Our temporary hires have been compensated and dismissed.
So mission accomplished?
Mission accomplished.
Thank you, Lewis.
You must be tired.
Please feel free to take the evening off.
Right.
Hey, Patterson.
We got our money's worth today.
Good.
From the state of things, it looks like it was quite the ordeal.
Where are William and the old man?
I believe they've already retired.
Albert has gone too.
Is that right?
That's a shame.
Then who on earth will I share this with?
You shouldn't have.
I declined an invitation from Lestrade because I wanted to come here instead.
So I'm going to indulge either way.
Join me?
I do have to say, I hope you didn't do anything untoward to the ladies at the tea party.
I wouldn't have had the time.
I was busy fulfilling my duties.
I don't believe it.
It almost sounds as though you've finally discovered the joy of labor.
Though I do feel like I've forgotten about something.
I wonder when their little tea party will be over.
I do still have plenty of these charming ring puzzles William gave me.
So I could spend an eternity down here if I so wished.
But surely they haven't all forgotten about me.
That would be ridiculous.
It could spend time with half an hour when they get on my head.
I feel lost, I feel lost
書きのくった手紙のことだけは覚えてない
It's so true, it's so true
気にすって私を恨まないで
2つに届けて 手のひらで踊る
代償にも一度 与えられるだろう
広いと風になる 午前後時
思い出を二人戻そう 最後の日に
美しさ望むなら迷うなと
罪を拭い去るように 終わらせて